简历预览 14-11-17 上午11:53

# Victor Zhang

male | Single | Born in 1990/9 | HUKOU: BEIJING

Location: OVERSEAS

>2 Years' Experience | Citizenship

Passport: G61708121

18601024483

E-mail: victorinhollywood@gmail.com

# Career Objective

#### Desired Type of Employment:

Full-time, Part-time, Intern

#### Desired Position:

Films/Media/Publication/Printing

#### Desired Industry:

Advertising/Exhibitions/Public Relations, Other, Computer Software, Internet/E-Commerce,

Media/Publication/Films

#### Desired Location:

BEIJING, United States

# Expected Salary (before tax):

Confidential

#### Current Situation:

student

#### Self-assessment

Studying major film, Two years experience in the Student Union, training a lot of communication and communication skills, Professional proficiency in the use of a variety of editing software, at the same time to grasp Photoshop, AE, Maya, 3Dmax.

## Project Experience

2012/05 -- 2013/08

#### Apple

Responsibilities (your responsibilities and achievements):

Specialist

2011/10 -- 2012/01

XingXing International Education

Responsibilities (your responsibilities and achievements):

Teaching Assistant

## **Education Background**



简历预览 14-11-17 上午11:53

2013/09-- 2014/10

New York Film Academy | Directing | Master

2009/09-- 2013/06

The Capital Normal University Of KEDE College | Radio and Television Editing & Directing

Bachelor

2006/06-- 2009/09

Ritan Middle School | aa | Senior High

Graduates Info.

College 1st Prize

Social Events

2001/05 -- 2001/09

Television Of KEDE

2001/05 -- 2001/09

Television Of KEDE

2001/06 -- 2001/10

Campus Reporter

2009/07 -- 2009/08

Volunteer of Italian Super Cup

2008/07 -- 2008/09

Youth Volunteer of The 29th Summer Olympic Games

## **Training**

2012/12--2013/02

Apple Inc.

Training Course: Apple Global retail development

Training Location: Beijing

2010/06--2011/12

Beijing Xing Xing International Animation Education

Training Course: 3D modeling
Training Location: Beijing

## Certificates

2012/01

简历预览 14-11-17 上午11:53

# Nationwide Lawyer Certificate

# Language Skills

English: reading&writing proficient | listening&speaking proficient

# Professional Skills

```
MAYA | basic | 12

Final Cut Pro | proficient | 24

iWork | proficient | 24

Microsoft Office | proficient | 24

| |
```